ANIRUDH SAINI

Content Writer | Digital Marketer

Uttam Nagar, Delhi •

+918571078587 •

anirudhsaini1600@gmail.com •

www.linkedin.com/in/anirudhs123•

PROFILE OVERVIEW -----

Technical Content Writer & Digital Content Writer with 2+ years' experience producing highimpact, ranking content across cloud, cybersecurity, and AI. Delivered 60+ articles (3K-9K words), driving organic traffic, top Google rankings, and brand authority. Proven success in SEO, guest posting, social media, and off-page strategies. Passionate About Content That Converts.

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS ------

❖ 60+ SEO blogs = 3x organic traffic

Ranked #1 on Google (U.S.)

❖ Boosted domain authority by 40% Improved organic conv. rates by 18%

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -----

BUZZCLAN (Technical Content Writer)

April 2024 – Present

- Writing over 25+ on-site comprehensive SEO-oriented Technical Blogs for BuzzClan, ranging from 3k-9k words, on subject domains, such as: Cloud, Data Engineering, QA, Cybersecurity, and 10 Other Pillars.
- Co-Development Software (1st U.S. Google Rank, driving traffic worth \$18k).

Data Analytics vs. Data Science

Adaptive Software Development

How Does A VPN Works

Penetration Testing

- Published 30+ high-DA technical guest posts on platforms like Cyber Defense Magazine (World's Biggest Cyber defense Magazine), Noupe, LearnWoo, etc.
- Managed company presence on LinkedIn (35K), YouTube, and Instagram; increased engagement by 65%
- Developed and executed backlink strategy; improved domain authority by 40%.
- Played a key role in planning and writing content for BuzzClan's AUA sessions, newsletters, and event campaigns.
- Performed off-page SEO activities using **Quora**, **Reddit**, and **Pinterest** (infographics).

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE -----

MY EQUATION

Content Writing Intern, September 2023 – December 2023

Assisted in making quality content for Social Media Platforms of "My Equation".

AASHMAN FOUNDATION

Content Writer, June 2023 – September 2023

Contributing English articles and blogs for the NGO's operational tasks.

KRSH WELFARE FOUNDATION Knowledge Analyst

Researched and wrote on positive psychology topics.

TEAM EVEREST NGO

Curriculum Developer, June 2023 – July 2023

Developed creative curriculum content for student engagement.

Social Media Marketing Intern, August 2022 – September 2022 **AASHMAN FOUNDATION**

Supported branding, digital marketing messaging and advertising campaigns.

EDUCATION ------ ADDITIONAL SKILLS ------

- CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY, MOHALI, INDIA Bachelors of Business Administration, June 2021 - 2024
- THAKUR DASS BHARGAVA SR. SEC. MODEL SCHOOL, HISAR, HARYANA 12th standard, April 2020 - 2021
- Content Writing
- Digital Marketing
- Transcription (typing)
- Creative Writing
- Bilingual in Spanish (beginner) and English (fluent)

Foundations of Digital Marketing (GOOGLE)

Introduction to Social Media Marketing (META)

Business English: Networking (COURSERA)

Learning how to learn (COURSERA)

Introduction to Psychology (COURSERA)

Attract Customers with Digital Marketing (GOOGLE)

Emotional and Social Intelligence (COURSERA)

Spanish by Culture Alley (CURSA)

Introduction to Soft Skills (TCS ION)

Building your personal brand (ASHRUST)